,file,title,title_sent_label,title_sent_score,article_sent_label,article_sent_score,pos_words,neg_words,entities
0,news_0047188.json,EMERGING MARKETS-Mexican peso seesaws over dollar; Argentina stocks hit record,['Neutral'],[0.0],['Positive'],[0.11],"['good, new, strong, latest, high, appreciated, first, real, more, major']","['expected, closed, down']",{'Argentina': 'GPE'}
1,news_0014010.json,"Migrants must visit Nazi concentration camps, Germany's Jewish council says",['Neutral'],[0.0],['Positive'],[0.11],"['new, more, newly, safe, first, high, live, legal, rose, sensitive, supporting']","['long, least, killed']","{'Nazi': 'NORP', 'Germany': 'GPE', 'Jewish council': 'ORG'}"
2,news_0042670.json,Euro zone businesses start 2018 on decade high,['Positive'],[0.16],['Positive'],[0.03],['high'],[''],"{'2018': 'DATE', 'decade': 'DATE'}"
3,news_0038485.json,Russia's Lavrov says 'unilateral actions' by US in Syria made Turkey furious: report - Reuters,['Negative'],[-0.5],['Negative'],[-0.08],"['best, new, many']","['destructive, unilateral, worst, foreign']","{'Russia': 'GPE', 'US': 'GPE', 'Syria': 'GPE', 'Turkey': 'GPE', 'Reuters': 'ORG'}"
4,news_0023363.json,Lawmakers to Justice Department: Keep online gambling legal,['Positive'],[0.2],['Positive'],[0.13],"['nearly, new, safe, safely, most, smart, available, legal, secure, responsibly, general, many']","['unlikely, closed, black, down']",{'Justice Department': 'ORG'}
5,news_0043962.json,FOREX -Dollar index slides to 3-year lows on broad-based weakness,['Neutral'],[0.0],['Positive'],[0.08],"['fresh, rose, large, powerful, nearly, first, much, high, kind, broadly, right, pretty, major']","['down, expected, common, negative, previously']","{'FOREX -Dollar': 'ORG', '3-year': 'DATE'}"
6,news_0036862.json,"Bio-Rad Gains Additional U.S. FDA Clearances for Blood Typing Products, Expanding its Offering for the Blood Testing Market",['Neutral'],[0.0],['Positive'],[0.09],"['certain, new, unique, pleased, direct, innovative, most, generally, offers, legal, more, broad, full']","['negative, wide, conventional, single']","{'Gains Additional U.S.': 'ORG', 'FDA Clearances': 'ORG'}"
7,news_0000403.json,"EQUITY ALERT: Levi & Korsinsky, LLP Reminds Shareholders of OSI Systems, Inc. of Commencement of a Class Action Lawsuit and a Lead Plaintiff Deadline of February 5, 2018",['Positive'],[0.1],['Negative'],[-0.13],"['new, action, free, more, allegedly, reasonable']","['false, :(, less, other, firm, criminal, illegal, failed, complaint, vulnerable']","{'Levi & Korsinsky': 'ORG', 'OSI Systems, Inc. of': 'ORG', 'February 5, 2018': 'DATE'}"
8,news_0056263.json,Japan Dec industrial output rises 2.7 pct mth/mth - METI,['Neutral'],[0.0],['Positive'],[0.2],"['full, straight, rose']",['previous'],"{'Japan Dec': 'ORG', '2.7': 'CARDINAL'}"
9,news_0032088.json,BRIEF-TDM Bhd Updates On Dec Production Figures,['Neutral'],[0.0],['Negative'],[-0.48],[''],"['crude, :(']",{}
